http://www.weemsgallery.com/terms-and-conditions

Sign InCreate AccountBookingsOrdersMy AccountSigned in as:filler@godaddy.comBookingsOrdersMy AccountSign outHomeShop Online ItemsGallery Frame ShopArtistAbout UsChristmasMoreHomeShop Online ItemsGallery Frame ShopArtistAbout UsChristmasSign InCreate AccountBookingsOrdersMy AccountSigned in as:filler@godaddy.comBookingsOrdersMy AccountSign outSigned in as:filler@godaddy.comHomeShop Online ItemsGallery Frame ShopArtistAbout UsChristmasAccountBookingsOrdersMy AccountSign outSign InBookingsOrdersMy Account
Terms and ConditionsWelcome to weemsgallery.com. We are located 7200 Montgomery Blvd NE Ste D; Albuquerque, NM 87109; 505-293-6133. As with most websites, we have put together some terms and conditions regarding using our website. For further information concerning this Website, please contact us at weems@weemsgallery.com or at 505-293-6133.IntroductionThese terms and conditions govern your use of this site; by using this site, you accept these terms and conditions in full. If you disagree with these terms and conditions or any part of these terms and conditions, you must not use this website. We may revise this Agreement at any time by updating this posting.Privacy StatementPlease review our Privacy Policy to understand in full our treatment of personal information and data.Access, Restrictions and License to use websiteUnless otherwise stated, Weems Gallery and Framing, LLC. and/or its licensors own the intellectual property rights in this website and material on the website; including artwork, graphics, photography, text, navigational buttons, meta-tags or "hidden text," etc... Any use of the website and its content for other than for shopping use is prohibited without written permission from Weems Gallery and Framing, LLC. Please do not reproduce, publish, display, modify, sell or distribute any materials from weemsgallery.com. You may, download, or electronically copy and print any of the page contents displayed on the site, but please remember that these are available for personal, noncommercial use only. Should you choose to download, copy, or forward any site materials via email or social media, no right, title, or interest in those materials will be transferred to you.You may be asked to provide personal information such as billing, shipping, and email addresses to access some of the resources this website offers or to order merchandise. All information you provide must be correct, current, and complete. By using this website, you authorize that all registration information you submit is correct, current, complete, truthful and accurate.Though this website is not intended for children under 18 years old, though we may sell products for children. Only with the involvement of an adult may a person under 18 use our services. We reserve the right to refuse service to anyone.You must not use this website in any way that causes, or may cause, damage to the website or impairment of the availability or accessibility of the website; or in anyway which is unlawful, illegal, fraudulent, or harmful or in connection with any unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful purpose or activity.You must not use this website to copy, store, host, transmit, send, use, publish or distribute any material which consists of (or is linked to) any spyware, computer virus, Trojan horse, worm, keystroke logger, rootkit or other malicious computer software.You must not conduct any systematic or automated data collection activities (including without limitation scrapping, data mining, data extraction and data harvesting) on or in relation to this website without Weems Gallery and Framing, LLC.'s written consent.AccuracyWeems Gallery and Framing, LLC. makes every possible effort to ensure information on this website is accurate and up to date. However, we cannot guarantee that all information contained in or made available through this website, including product descriptions is accurate, complete, reliable, current or error-free. We assume no liability or responsibility for any errors or omissions in the content of this website, ancillary materials or communication. Prices are based upon current artist rates and are subject to change. Prices on any art you can’t purchase online are not guaranteed without calling for a current price.Risk of LossAll products purchased from Weems Gallery and Framing, LLC. shipped via SSG's carrier contracts and are insured through their delivery. Risk of loss and damage for purchased products pass along to you upon delivery.If a purchased product is lost during shipment, we will replace with an identical or similar item, dictated by the insurance claim.Disclaimers and LimitationsDue to the unpredictability of technology and the Internet environment, Weems Gallery and Framing, LLC. cannot guarantee that files downloaded from the Internet will be free of viruses, worms, Trojan horses, or other code that manifests contaminating or destructive activities. You assume responsibility for any costs accumulated with the servicing of equipment used in connection with this website. As our visitor, you agree that your access is subject to the terms and conditions set forth in this legal notice and that using this website is at your own risk. Weems Gallery and Framing, LLC. is not liable for any damages related to your use or inability to access the website.If you have any questions about our Terms and Conditions, please contact us.By e-mail: weems@weemsgallery.com
By Phone: 505-2936133
7200 Montgomery Blvd NE Ste DAlbuquerque, NM 87109We reserve the right to make changes to this policy.  Any changes to this policy will be posted before they take effect.
Copyright © 2020 Weems Gallery & Framing - All Rights Reserved.Powered by GoDaddy Website BuilderArtist SubmissionTerms and ConditionsPrivacy PolicyShipping & Ordering
